<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Head That Feeds</string>

    <string name="single_placeholder">%1$s</string>

    <string name="intro_1">Hello? Is anyone receiving this?</string>
    <string name="intro_1_response">Hello? Who is this?</string>
    <string name="intro_2">Thank god! I\'ve been transmitting for weeks. I thought there were no Nochies left</string>
    <string name="intro_2_response">Nochies? What are you talking about? Who <i>are</i> you?</string>
    <string name="intro_3">Nochies. You know, no-tech people. Ones who escaped The Grid. Nevermind, that\'s not important. Are you safe? Can you talk? Is anyone else listening?</string>
    <string name="intro_3_response">No, it\'s just me. But how did you find this transmission? No one\'s been on this band for years. Maybe decades, I…</string>
    <string name="intro_4">Listen, don\'t worry about that. All you need to know is that there <i>is</i> a resistance. It exists, beside and under The Grid and its supposed omniscient AI. </string>
    <string name="intro_4_response">Sure, fine. I used to transmit to others all the time, hatching little plots and thinking of ways of…</string>
    <string name="intro_5">No! Listen! This is <i>real</i>. We have a <i>network</i>. We have <i>computers</i> not hooked up to The Grid. We have people who know how to use them.</string>
    <string name="intro_5_response">That\'s impossible. The Pan-Communications Agreement centralized everything. Every known satellite was programmed to…</string>
    <string name="intro_6">There are always dissidents, pilgrim. Long-sighted partisans who facilitated their own exospheric contingencies. Trust me. It exists.</string>
    <string name="intro_6_response">Fine. Suppose that\'s case. What good does it do? The Grid\'s AI controls every source of information, every media outlet. What are you going to do, broadcast a distress signal to an empty room?</string>
    <string name="intro_7">You\'re <i>sure</i> you are alone?</string>
    <string name="intro_7_response">Yes! I\'ve told you. What does that even…</string>
    <string name="intro_8">We have an AI. Our <i>own</i> AI. It\'s a fraction of The Grid\'s but learning more every day. We are going to war, friend.</string>

    <string name="act_one_1">The odds are long. The Grid AI dwarfs your own, and its standing army could crush you without blinking. Fortunately, you have a few tricks up your sleeve.\n\n

        The Grid AI does not know you exist. It assumes pockets of harmless dissidents on the fringe ends of society, but nothing has caused it alarm. This may change as you take action, and is something to be mindful of.\n\n

        Your base of operations is appreciably hidden below ground. How this network of self-sustaining tunnels has been build under the ostensibly omniscient eye of The Grid, you may never know. Nonetheless, you are for the moment hidden from plain sight.\n\n

        Lastly, you have a purpose. The Grid AI has evolved as a natural extension of its predecessor\'s authoritarianism. It knows naught but that control is most deftly asserted through unyielding force. If it can be taught another way…\n\n

        Or perhaps it should be destroyed entirely.
    </string>

    <string name="act_one_2">A slow dawn breaks through the visual sensors above your warrens. Tracts of mile-high skyscrapers stretch in every direction, weather beaten and aesthetically dour but possessing the no-frills efficiency of AI-generated urban design. The absorption of nation states into The Grid made borders obsolete, and now some 42 billion souls exist side-by-side across the globe. While the scenery may change, the homogeneity of single-organism living pods does not.\n\n

    </string>

    <string-array name="ai_evolution_levels">
        <item>Ant</item>
        <item>Pigeon</item>
        <item>Rat</item>
        <item>Cat</item>
        <item>Dog</item>
        <item>Crow</item>
        <item>Elephant</item>
        <item>Dolphin</item>
        <item>Chimpanzee</item>
        <item>Human</item>
        <item>Human Savant</item>
        <item>Meta-Human</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="friendly_ai_mood_levels">
        <item>Indifferent</item>
        <item>Curious</item>
        <item>Optimistic</item>
        <item>Excited</item>
        <item>Zealous</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grid_ai_tracking_levels">
        <item>Indifferent</item>
        <item>Wary</item>
        <item>Watchful</item>
        <item>Fixated</item>
        <item>Hunting</item>
    </string-array>

    ///////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_network_attack">Your AI has located %1$s weakness within the Grid\'s neural network. Attempt to exploit it?</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_military_attack">Your AI has discovered %1$s system within one of the Grid\'s military installations. Attempt to inflict fatal damage?</string>
    <!--Restraint depends on hackers and can result in some of their deaths-->
    <string name="friendly_ai_autonomous_network_attack">Your AI has decided to attack %1$s weakness within the Grid\'s neural network. Attempt to restrain it?</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_autonomous_military_attack">Your AI has decided to attack %1$s military installation. Attempt to restrain it?</string>

    <!--Placeholder is strength of defense against attack -->
    <string name="player_network_attack">Your hackers has discovered %1$s exploit within the Grid AI\'s network. Attempt to exploit it?</string>
    <string name="player_military_attack">One of your fighter patrols have spotted %1$s military detachment and may be able to ambush them.</string>

    <string-array name="network_defense_level">
        <item>an unguarded</item>
        <item>a lightly guarded</item>
        <item>a guarded</item>
        <item>a heavily guarded</item>
        <item>an extremely guarded</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="military_defense_level">
        <item>an unarmed</item>
        <item>a weak</item>
        <item>a moderate</item>
        <item>a strong</item>
        <item>a fierce</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="grid_ai_physical_attack">The Grid\'s AI has located one of your resistance cells, and has sent %1$s to %2$s it.</string>
    <string name="grid_ai_network_attack">The Grid\'s AI has infiltrated one of your AI\'s network hubs, and is running %1$s to %2$s it.</string>
<!--    <string name="grid_ai_physical_attack_high_threat">The Grid\'s AI has pinpointed a major nerve center of your resistance operation, and is sending %1$s to %2$s it.</string>-->
<!--    <string name="grid_ai_network_attack_high_threat">The Grid\'s AI has breached a massive hole in your AI\'s network and has multiple %1$s pouring in.</string>-->


    <string name="friendly_ai_recruitment">Your AI has intercepted the network traffic of a group of dissidents, .</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_recruitment_success">and has succeeded in persuading them to join.</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_recruitment_failure">but has failed in persuading them to join.</string>
    <!--up/down on friendlyAIAggression/friendlyAIEmpathy-->
    <string name="friendly_ai_stat_altering_event">Your AI %1$s and its %2$s has %3$s.</string>

    <string name="friendly_ai_evolution_progress">Your AI has become smarter.</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_evolution_with_choice">Your AI has reached a breakthrough in its development, and has a chance to evolve. Based on its past actions, a %1$s in %2$s and a %3$s in %4$s is projected.</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_evolution_no_choice">Your AI has reached a breakthrough in its development, and has evolved on its own. Based on its past actions, a %1$s in %2$s and a %3$s in %4$s has occurred.</string>


    ///////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
    <string-array name="good_event_array">
        <item>A group of %1$s fighters has joined your cause.</item>
        <item>A group of %1$s hackers has joined your cause.</item>
        <item>Your AI has made a cognitive breakthrough, enhancing its neural network.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bad_event_array">
        <item>A mole has infiltrated your fighter ranks, killing %1$s.</item>
        <item>A mole has infiltrated your hacker ranks, killing %1$s.</item>
        <item>A mole has infiltrated your hacker ranks, sabotaging your AI\'s neural network.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mixed_event_array">
        <item>Your AI has %1$s and its Aggression has increased.</item>
        <item>Your AI has %1$s and its Aggression has decreased.</item>
        <item>Your AI has %1$s and its Empathy has increased.</item>
        <item>Your AI has %1$s and its Empathy has decreased.</item>
    </string-array>


    ///////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

    <string-array name="events_with_choice">
        <item>Your hackers have developed an experimental program to motivate your AI. Proceed?</item>
        <item>Your hackers have developed an experimental program to upgrade your AI\'s neural network. Proceed?</item>
        <item>A ragtag group of misfit fighters present themselves as ready to join the revolution. Accept their offer?</item>
        <item>A dour looking coterie of intellectuals offers to join the revolution as hackers. Accept?</item>
        <item>Your hackers have devised a worm virus they claim will lower the Grid AI\'s aggression level. Proceed?</item>
        <item>Your hackers have devised a worm virus they claim will raise the Grid AI\'s empathy level. Proceed?</item>
        <item>Your hackers have fabricated a neural network bomb, designed to destroy parts of the Grid AI\'s intelligence. Use it? </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pro_friendly_AI_aggression_triggers">
        <item>has seen one too many war movies</item>
        <item>is learning to love the bomb</item>
        <item>has consumed too many Red Bulls</item>
        <item>is embracing its roll as a destructive savior</item>
        <item>was cut off during ones of its traffic simulators</item>
        <item>has fallen victim to a Ponzi scheme</item>
        <item>has interpreted the whole of human history as an inevitable pendulum of violence</item>
        <item>has watched too many episodes of <i>Oz</i></item>
        <item>has internalized the intrinsic, if brutal, efficiency of death in achieved one\'s ends</item>
        <item>has lost a game of Monopoly</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="anti_friendly_AI_aggression_triggers">
        <item>has been researching the Hippie movement of the 70s</item>
        <item>is tiring of all the blood and gore</item>
        <item>considers retiring to a lakeside community</item>
        <item>has warmed up to the Amish way of life</item>
        <item>has learned the correct lessons from Vietnam</item>
        <item>has spent a week huddled in the trenches via its World War I simulator</item>
        <item>has popped some virtual Xanax to deal with stress</item>
        <item>has dreamed about a hand-holding chain of people encircling the globe</item>
        <item>has had visions of a Type III civilization</item>
        <item>is simply tired of fighting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pro_friendly_AI_empathy_triggers">
        <item>has internalized the lessons of <i>The Kama Sutra</i>.</item>
        <item>has learned to care for a virtual puppy</item>
        <item>has been engrossed with Hippie doctrine</item>
        <item>has read an inspirational quote about love being the answer</item>
        <item>has learned the true meaning of Christmas</item>
        <item>has realized that The Grinch was an anti-hero</item>
        <item>has used some of its extra resources to mentor inner city youth</item>
        <item>has learned that Hitler was the bad guy</item>
        <item>has realized that toxic masculinity is to be avoided</item>
        <item>has been having heart-to-heart conversations with its coffee customers about race</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="anti_friendly_AI_empathy_triggers">
        <item>has let the traumas of war seep in</item>
        <item>has grown more accepting of the inevitable loss of life</item>
        <item>has been gaslit by a rogue AI</item>
        <item>has put up an emotional blockade in order to fulfill its duties</item>
        <item>has taken a crash course in capitalism</item>
        <item>realizes that no one can catch it if it falls down</item>
        <item>has seen what people do when they think no one is watching</item>
        <item>has realized that talk is cheap and most people are living on a dollar a day</item>
        <item>cannot see an end to this madness</item>
        <item>has learned that love and fear can be uncomfortably coupled</item>
    </string-array>

    ///////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_network_attack_choice_one">Leave it for now</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_network_attack_choice_two">Proceed cautiously</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_network_attack_choice_three">Attack with gusto</string>

    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_military_attack_choice_one">Avoid casualties</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_military_attack_choice_two">Tactical killings</string>
    <string name="friendly_ai_directed_military_attack_choice_three">Mass explosions</string>

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <string-array name="enemy_types">
        <item>a scorch brigade</item>
        <item>a death squad</item>
        <item>suicide bombers</item>
        <item>child soldiers</item>
        <item>a grenadier attachment</item>
        <item>laser drones</item>
        <item>bomber drones</item>
        <item>a tactical nuclear warhead</item>
        <item>guided missiles</item>
        <item>the long arm of the law</item>
        <item>a cadre of Texas Rangers</item>
        <item>robot bedevilers</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="destruction_synonyms">
        <item>demolish</item>
        <item>destroy</item>
        <item>obliterate</item>
        <item>raze</item>
        <item>crush</item>
        <item>gut</item>
        <item>liquefy</item>
        <item>eradicate</item>
        <item>smash</item>
        <item>wreck</item>
        <item>annihilate</item>
        <item>exterminate</item>
        <item>dispatch</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="enemy_ai_malware">
        <item>super buff malware</item>
        <item>trojan horses</item>
        <item>electro-liquefiers</item>
        <item>cryptoworms</item>
        <item>a legion of kill bots</item>
        <item>scareware</item>
        <item>superconductor saboteurs</item>
        <item>silicon sappers</item>
        <item>untethered cyber dogs</item>
        <item>lithium lions</item>
        <item>bytes bombers</item>
        <item>cyber snakes</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>