<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Head That Feeds</string>

    <string name="intro_1">Hello? Is anyone receiving this?</string>
    <string name="intro_1_response">Hello? Who is this?</string>
    <string name="intro_2">Thank god! I\'ve been transmitting for weeks. I thought there were no Nochies left</string>
    <string name="intro_2_response">Nochies? What are you talking about? Who <i>are</i> you?</string>
    <string name="intro_3">Nochies. You know, no-tech people. Ones who escaped The Grid. Nevermind, that\'s not important. Are you safe? Can you talk? Is anyone else listening?</string>
    <string name="intro_3_response">No, it\'s just me. But how did you find this transmission? No one\'s been on this band for years. Maybe decades, I…</string>
    <string name="intro_4">Listen, don\'t worry about that. All you need to know is that there <i>is</i> a resistance. It exists, beside and under The Grid and its supposed omniscient AI. </string>
    <string name="intro_4_response">Sure, fine. I used to transmit to others all the time, hatching little plots and thinking of ways of…</string>
    <string name="intro_5">No! Listen! This is <i>real</i>. We have a <i>network</i>. We have <i>computers</i> not hooked up to The Grid. We have people who know how to use them.</string>
    <string name="intro_5_response">That\'s impossible. The Pan-Communications Agreement centralized everything. Every known satellite was programmed to…</string>
    <string name="intro_6">There are always dissidents, pilgrim. Long-sighted partisans who facilitated their own exospheric contingencies. Trust me. It exists.</string>
    <string name="intro_6_response">Fine. Suppose that\'s case. What good does it do? The Grid\'s AI controls every source of information, every media outlet. What are you going to do, broadcast a distress signal to an empty room?</string>
    <string name="intro_7">You\'re <i>sure</i> you are alone?</string>
    <string name="intro_7_response">Yes! I\'ve told you. What does that even…</string>
    <string name="intro_8">We have an AI. Our <i>own</i> AI. It\'s a fraction of The Grid\'s but learning more every day. We are going to war, friend.</string>

    <string-array name="player_ai_levels">
        <item>Ant</item>
        <item>Pigeon</item>
        <item>Rat</item>
        <item>Cat</item>
        <item>Dog</item>
        <item>Crow</item>
        <item>Elephant</item>
        <item>Dolphin</item>
        <item>Chimpanzee</item>
        <item>Human</item>
        <item>Human Savant</item>
        <item>Post-Human Evolution</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="enemy_ai_levels">
        <item>Indifferent</item>
        <item>Wary</item>
        <item>Watchful</item>
        <item>Fixated</item>
        <item>Hunting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="enemy_activity_levels">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Sparse</item>
        <item>Moderate</item>
        <item>Heavy</item>
        <item>Overwhelming</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>